<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Publications | AI Health</title><link>/publication/</link><atom:link href="/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Publications</description><generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 19:56:28 -0500</lastBuildDate><image><url>/img/icon-192.png</url><title>Publications</title><link>/publication/</link></image><item><title>Ai Health Data Challenge</title><link>/publication/ai-health-data-challenge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 19:56:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>/publication/ai-health-data-challenge/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are up for the AI Health Data Challenge, read on for the details.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
It is our goal to foster collaboration among disciplines and promote data-driven, evidence-based care.
We are looking for UT students from diverse backgrounds with skills in information science, computer
science, and medical science, to leverage their collective knowledge as a team and create an app for
mining large datasets of electronic medical records. The app should produce valuable knowledge to
support clinical decision making and present it through an effortless, immediate interface.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;How to access the data&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The challenge is based on the MIMIC-III database. All participants must use this dataset. There is a
formal process for requesting access to MIMIC-III found here:
&lt;a href=&#34;https://mimic.physionet.org/gettingstarted/access/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://mimic.physionet.org/gettingstarted/access/&lt;/a&gt;. You will need to pass the Human Subject Online
Course from MIT in order to get permission to download the dataset. This process can take several days,
so plan accordingly. Participants must agree to the MIMIC-III data use agreement. Please submit the
completion report (not the certificate).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;How to submit the deliverables&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Please submit the following items before 11PM Central Time March 2
nd
, 2020 to XYZ email:&lt;br&gt;
● A 2-5 page report on the details of how you built the app. This report should contain the link to
your GitHub, the details of your methods, and screenshots of your app.&lt;br&gt;
● 5-minute video about your process.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Finalists will be announced on April 2, 2020. They will present their apps to a panel of health care
experts on May 1, 2020, who will choose the winner at the end of the day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
To participate and connect with potential teammates, register by filling in this google form XYZ before
Dec 1, 2019.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;How to win&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Your submission will be shortlisted by UT Austin faculty by March 22, 2020. The top teams will be invited
to participate in a day-long seminar on April 3, 2020, where each team will present their work to a jury
of healthcare professionals.&lt;br&gt;
The judging criteria are:&lt;br&gt;
● Usability&lt;br&gt;
● Novelty&lt;br&gt;
● Reproducibility&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;What you’ll win&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1st prize: $1500; 2nd prize: $500&lt;br&gt;
The two winning submissions will be made available on the AI Health website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Deadlines&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
● Register at XYZ google form by December 1, 2019&lt;br&gt;
● Final submission due by 11pm CST on March 2, 2020&lt;br&gt;
● Announcement of finalists: March 22, 2020&lt;br&gt;
● Presentation and judging: April 3, 2020&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>